Will & Harper is a documentary, comedy film directed by Josh Greenbaum.
When Will Ferrell's good friend Harper comes out as a trans woman, they take a road
trip to bond and reintroduce Harper to the country as her true self.
Self, played by Will Ferrell.
Self, played by Harper Steele.
Self, played by Tim Meadows.
Self, played by Seth Meyers.
Self, played by Kristen Wiig.
Self, played by Colin Jost.
Will & Harper is a 2024 American documentary film directed by Josh Greenbaum and following actor Will Ferrell and writer Harper Steele
as the duo make a 17-day road trip across the United States, the latter having recently completed a gender transition.
It was produced by Jessica Elbaum, Ferrell, Greenbaum,
Christopher Leggett, and Rafael Marmor.
Will & Harper premiered at the 40th Sundance Film Festival on January 22, 2024, received a limited theatrical
release in the United States on September 13, and began streaming worldwide on Netflix on September 27.
It received positive reviews from critics and was named one of the top 5
documentary films of 2024 by the National Board of Review.
The film won a Peabody Award at the 85th Annual Ceremony.
The film received a BAFTA nomination for Best
Documentary at the 2025 BAFTA Film Awards.
The film explores themes of friendship, road trip,
lgbt, human interest, trans woman.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.